<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Expandable ListView</string>

    <string-array name="department_Name_Header">

        <item> Computer </item>
        <item> Electrical </item>
        <item> Electronics </item>
        <item> Marine </item>
        <item> AutoMobile </item>
        <item> ShipBuilding </item>
        <item> Mechanical </item>
        <item> Power </item>
        <item> Architecture </item>
        <item> Civil </item>
        <item> Garments Design</item>
        <item> Textile </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="department_Details_Child">

        <item> A computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

        <item> B computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

        <item> C computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

        <item> D computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

        <item> E computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

        <item> F computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

        <item> G computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

        <item> H computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

        <item> I computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

        <item> J computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

        <item> K computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

        <item> L computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming. Modern computers have the
            ability to follow generalized sets of operations, called programs. A "complete" computer including the hardware, the operating system, and peripheral equipment required and used
            for "full" operation can be referred to as a computer system. </item>

    </string-array>

</resources>
